const sports = [
    { "question": "What science did Aristotle define as 'the knowledge of immaterial being'?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Metaphysics", "choices": ["Psychology", "Logic", "Metaphysics", "Philosophy"] },
    { "question": "Which WWF group does this theme music belong to?", "category": "sports", "answer": "D-Generation X", "choices": ["Nation of Domination", "D-Generation X", "Legion of Doom", "Hart Foundation"] },
    { "question": "What position is former Major League Baseball player, Rollie Fingers famous for playing?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Pitcher", "choices": ["Catcher", "First Base", "Pitcher", "Third Base"] },
    { "question": "What position is former baseball player for the Cincinnati Reds, Johnny Bench famous for playing?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Catcher", "choices": ["Second Base", "Shortstop", "Catcher", "Pitcher"] },
    { "question": "Baltimore Orioles, Cal Ripken Jr. is most known for playing what position?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Shortstop", "choices": ["Right Field", "Catcher", "Pitcher", "Shortstop"] },
    { "question": "Steve Garvey is a famous former baseball player, who is known for playing what position?", "category": "sports", "answer": "First Base", "choices": ["First Base", "Shortstop", "Third Base", "Catcher"] },
    { "question": "What position is former Major League Baseball player, Joe Morgan most known to have played?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Second Base", "choices": ["Outfield", "None of these", "Second Base", "Catcher"] },
    { "question": "What position is former professional baseball player, Mike Schmidt famous for playing?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Third Base", "choices": ["Pitcher", "Catcher", "Third Base", "Second Base"] },
    { "question": "Which of these positions is former baseball player, Dwight Evans most famous for?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Right Field", "choices": ["Right Field", "Pitcher", "Second Base", "Center Field"] },
    { "question": "Successful Major League Baseball player and coach, Donald Edward Don Gullett, was famous for playing what position?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Pitcher", "choices": ["Pitcher", "Second Base", "Right Field", "Catcher"] },
    { "question": "Whitey Ford was a successful Major League Baseball player, who played in what position?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Pitcher", "choices": ["Pitcher", "First Base", "Catcher", "Shortstop"] },
    { "question": "Carlton Fisk was a successful Major League Baseball player, who played for 24 years with the Boston Red Sox and Chicago White Sox, in what position?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Catcher", "choices": ["Catcher", "Pitcher", "Left Field", "None of the Above"] },
    { "question": "The Pittsburgh Steelers of the 50s had a third string quarterback from Louisville, who was not making it. They cut him and he landed with the Colts. Who was he?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Johnny Unitas", "choices": ["Terry Bradshaw", "Bert Jones Jr", "Len Dawson", "Johnny Unitas"] },
    { "question": "Which was the first football team to win back to back Super Bowls with different coaches?", "category": "sports", "answer": "San Francisco", "choices": ["San Francisco", "Dallas", "Miami", "Pittsburgh"] },
    { "question": "How many points did Wilt Chamberlain score in his best game versus New York?", "category": "sports", "answer": "100", "choices": ["71", "100", "82", "99"] },
    { "question": "He is the youngest NBA player to score 10,000 points.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Kobe Bryant", "choices": ["Spud Webb", "Kobe Bryant", "Moses Malone", "Michael Jordon"] },
    { "question": "He is the shortest player ever to win the Slam Dunk Contest.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Spud Webb", "choices": ["Kobe Bryant", "Spud Webb", "Vince Carter", "Tracy McGrady"] },
    { "question": "He retired with the NBA's highest scoring average (30.1 points per game).", "category": "sports", "answer": "Michael Jordan", "choices": ["Jarmaine ONeal", "Shaquille ONeal", "Dwyane Wade", "Michael Jordan"] },
    { "question": "Karl Malone received the award Most Valuable Player in 1996-97. What team did he play for?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Utah Jazz", "choices": ["Sacramento Kings", "Miami Heat", "LA Lakers", "Utah Jazz"] },
    { "question": "He is the NBA's All-Time scorer.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "choices": ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "Ken Johnson", "Clyde Lovelette", "Michael Jordan"] },
    { "question": "Wilt Chamberlain is a great player indeed. In a game against the Celtics he made the best rebounding effort ever. How many rebounds did he make in this famous game?", "category": "sports", "answer": "55", "choices": ["16", "57", "55", "31"] },
    { "question": "Who is the first player to top 20,000 points in NBA?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Bob Pettit", "choices": ["Bob Pettit", "Spud Webb", "Clyde Drexler", "Wilt Chamberlain"] },
    { "question": "George Muresan and Manute Bol are the tallest players in NBA history. How tall are they?", "category": "sports", "answer": "77 (2.31m)", "choices": ["77 (2.31m)", "72 (2.18m)", "78 (2.33m)", "74 (2.23m)"] },
    { "question": "Who is the shortest player in the history of NBA?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Tyronne Bogues", "choices": ["Tyronne Bogues", "Spud Webb", "Larry Bird", "Eddie Griffin"] },
    { "question": "He was a player, coach, and owner - all for one team. He was also instrumental in developing the NFL.", "category": "sports", "answer": "George Halas", "choices": ["Wellington Mara", "George Halas", "Red Grange", "Pete Rozelle"] },
    { "question": "This college and pro great had a very strange nickname - Crazy Legs. His last name was Hirsch. What was his real first name?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Elroy", "choices": ["Lester", "Arnie", "Cliff", "Elroy"] },
    { "question": "Compton Junior College gave us this all-time great runner, who played fullback and was nicknamed Joe the Jet.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Perry", "choices": ["Battles", "Neale", "Sanders", "Perry"] },
    { "question": "His real name is Yelverton Abraham, and he played for San Francisco as well as the NY Giants. He attended LSU.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Tittle", "choices": ["Motley", "Strong", "Groza", "Tittle"] },
    { "question": "This great sportsman was the first football player to be all-pro at defensive back one year and running back another.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Gifford", "choices": ["Grange", "Thorpe", "Gifford", "Haynes"] },
    { "question": "This quarterback was cut by the Steelers and picked up by another team, played in high tops, and his teammates include Lenny Moore and Steve Myhra.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Johnny Unitas", "choices": ["Terry Bradshaw", "Johnny Unitas", "John Brodie", "Norm Van Brocklin"] },
    { "question": "This great defensive end came from South Carolina State and played for the Rams. He is credited with inventing the head slap move.", "category": "sports", "answer": "David Jones", "choices": ["Lamar Lundy", "David Jones", "Merlin Olsen", "Rosy Grier"] },
    { "question": "This great running back was once traded for eleven players. He had great speed and great moves, returned kicks, caught passes, and ran the ball.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Ollie Matson", "choices": ["Barry Sanders", "Ollie Matson", "Dick Lane", "Marcus Allen"] },
    { "question": "This great football player is known for catching the immaculate reception.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Franco Harris", "choices": ["Franco Harris", "Lynn Swann", "John Stallworth", "Terry Bradshaw"] },
    { "question": "This great football player won the Heisman Trophy in 1975 and played for the Denver Broncos.", "category": "sports", "answer": "John Elway", "choices": ["Marcus Allen", "Bo Jackson", "John Elway", "Jim Thorpe"] },
    { "question": "This quarterback led the Chicago Bears to a Super Bowl victory, and his nickname was The Refrigerator.", "category": "sports", "answer": "William Perry", "choices": ["William Perry", "Jim McMahon", "Ronnie Lott", "Walter Payton"] },
    { "question": "This former quarterback's name is synonymous with the Dallas Cowboys. He was a part of the original team.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Roger Staubach", "choices": ["Roger Staubach", "Troy Aikman", "Don Meredith", "Danny White"] },
    { "question": "This linebacker was drafted by the Baltimore Ravens, but he was once a quarterback at Michigan State.", "category": "sports", "answer": "Ray Lewis", "choices": ["Lawrence Taylor", "Brian Urlacher", "Ray Lewis", "Deion Sanders"] },
    { "question": "What is the name of the basketball tournament held annually for college teams in the United States?", "category": "sports", "answer": "NCAA Tournament", "choices": ["NCAA Tournament", "NBA Playoffs", "College World Series", "Little League World Series"] },
    { "question": "Which Major League Baseball player holds the record for the most home runs in a single season?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Barry Bonds", "choices": ["Babe Ruth", "Mark McGwire", "Barry Bonds", "Hank Aaron"] },
    { "question": "What sport is associated with the terms 'love', 'deuce', and 'set'?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Tennis", "choices": ["Tennis", "Rugby", "Football", "Cricket"] },
    { "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 2014?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Germany", "choices": ["Argentina", "Germany", "Brazil", "Spain"] },
    { "question": "Which sport is known as 'the beautiful game'?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Soccer", "choices": ["Basketball", "Baseball", "Soccer", "Hockey"] },
    { "question": "What is the highest score possible in a game of ten-pin bowling?", "category": "sports", "answer": "300", "choices": ["100", "200", "250", "300"] },
    { "question": "How many players are on a standard soccer team?", "category": "sports", "answer": "11", "choices": ["7", "9", "10", "11"] },
    { "question": "In which sport would you perform a slam dunk?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Basketball", "choices": ["Basketball", "Baseball", "Soccer", "Football"] },
    { "question": "Which sport features the terms 'birdie', 'eagle', and 'par'?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Golf", "choices": ["Golf", "Tennis", "Rugby", "Cricket"] },
    { "question": "What is the most popular sport in the world?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Soccer", "choices": ["Basketball", "Cricket", "Soccer", "Hockey"] },
    { "question": "What is the distance of a marathon race?", "category": "sports", "answer": "26.2 miles", "choices": ["13.1 miles", "26.2 miles", "20 miles", "30 miles"] },
    { "question": "What is the national sport of Canada?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Lacrosse", "choices": ["Ice Hockey", "Lacrosse", "Basketball", "Soccer"] },
    { "question": "In which sport would you find a 'shuttlecock'?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Badminton", "choices": ["Tennis", "Badminton", "Table Tennis", "Baseball"] },
    { "question": "Which sport uses a 'bat' to hit a 'ball'?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Baseball", "choices": ["Tennis", "Baseball", "Golf", "Basketball"] },
    { "question": "What is the name of the annual championship game of the National Football League?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Super Bowl", "choices": ["World Series", "Super Bowl", "NBA Finals", "Stanley Cup"] },
    { "question": "In baseball, how many outs are there in an inning?", "category": "sports", "answer": "6", "choices": ["3", "6", "4", "5"] },
    { "question": "Which sport is played on a rectangular field with a goal at each end?", "category": "sports", "answer": "Soccer", "choices": ["Football", "Soccer", "Rugby", "Cricket"] }
];
